Back-to-nature chills and thrills!
Scooby-Doo! Camp Scare is a animation, comedy,
family film directed by Ethan Spaulding.
Scooby and the gang experience outdoor fun as they
go back to Fred's old summer camp.
As summer goes on, it becomes increasingly clear that the spooky camp stories told by the fireplace, are more
real than they've though and soon, it's up to the gang to try and solve the mystery of camp scare.
Fred / Scooby Doo (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Velma (voice), played by Mindy Cohn.
Shaggy (voice), played by Matthew Lillard.
Daphne (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Ranger Knudsen / Woodsman / Spectre / Fishman
(voice), played by Dee Bradley Baker.
Deacon / Babyface Boretti / Store Owner (voice), played by Mark Hamill.
Scooby-Doo!
Camp Scare is a 2010 direct-to-video animated comedy horror-mystery film; the fifteenth direct-to-video film
based upon the Scooby-Doo Saturday morning cartoon, and was released on September 14, 2010.
The film was released seven months after the release of Scooby-Doo!
Abracadabra-Doo.
The 15th direct-to-video Scooby-Doo film, the film sold 53,389 units in its first
week and as of January 2013, it has sold approximately 194,000 units.
The film explores themes of summer camp, fisherman,
talking dog, campfire story, fishman.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.